<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<sector boes="2.0.0">
    <name>Za-Khazi Run, North</name>
    <comment>Comment</comment>
    <encounter can-flee="false" force="true">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>168</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>8</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </encounter>
    <wandering can-flee="true" force="false">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>171</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </wandering>
    <wandering can-flee="false" force="false">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>171</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>168</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </wandering>
    <wandering can-flee="false" force="false">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>133</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </wandering>
    <area top="1" left="20" bottom="4" right="25">Below Khoth&apos;s Fortress</area>
    <area top="27" left="36" bottom="30" right="38">Near Broken Fang Clan</area>
    <area top="12" left="2" bottom="45" right="31">Slimy Tunnels</area>
    <string id="0">
        <![CDATA[You were starting to take free passage down this river a little bit for granted. Sure, there were rapids and falls, but no places where creatures were actually preventing you from passing. Until now.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="1">
        <![CDATA[A fortress has been built here, spanning a narrow region of the river. The river passes underneath. You can take your boat inside, but you can't be sure they will let you pass.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="2">
        <![CDATA[You look up onto the ramparts of the fort, and see several troglodytes pacing back and forth on patrol. When they spot you, they laugh and make certain hand gestures. So much for a warm welcome.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="6">
        <![CDATA[With great relief, you row away from the troglodyte's fortress. The river carries you into a large, tranquil lake. By now, you must finally be near the end of the Za-Khazi Run.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="7">
        <![CDATA[Your period of speedy progress was all too brief, and has come to an end. The river has become very rocky and treacherous. You may not be able to navigate it safely for much longer.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="8">
        <![CDATA[Up on the hills to the north of the river, you see a  massive granite fortress. At first, you think it might be Fort Cavalier. No such luck. Nobody mans the battlements, and nobody in Exile has ever made a structure that dark and grim.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="9">
        <![CDATA[Going any farther west would only mean a quick death on the rapids. You pole the barge backward quickly, before you get caught in the flow and smashed to bits.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="10">
        <![CDATA[To the east, you can see a narrow path. It leads around a large forest of stalagmites and into a fort. The fort is built over a narrow part of the river, blocking it.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="11">
        <![CDATA[These tunnels are very similar to the tunnels you've been wandering through for the last few days. There's only one big difference. The walls, floors, and even the ceiling are covered with a thin layer of slime.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="12">
        <![CDATA[It must have taken years to cover all these miles of tunnels with slime, top to bottom. These passages must have all kinds of icky creatures in them.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="13">
        <![CDATA[At the lowest point of this long passage, you find a veritable sea of slime. It's a fifty foot wide pool of mucous-like substance, green and ten feet deep.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="14">
        <![CDATA[Writhing around in the sea are many huge wyrms. Bigger than huge. Immense. Fifty feet long each. They wiggle around in the slime, occasionally rearing up to grab a bat, lizard, or smaller wyrm.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="15">
        <![CDATA[They seem unaware of your presence. Of course, you could pick a fight.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="19">
        <![CDATA[You walk up to one of the closer creatures and start hitting it. It screeches in alarm, and soon you have all of the things on top of you ...]]>
    </string>
    <string id="20">
        <![CDATA[You're covered with blood and muck, and every muscle in your bodies is sore. The last of the creatures is dead. Victory is yours.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="21">
        <![CDATA[At first, you think that none of them have any treasure. Then you figure, since you're covered with muck anyway, you might as well look in their stomachs. Sure enough, you find a wicked, curved blade, still in the sheathe, inside one of the wyrms.]]>
    </string>
</sector>
