<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<sector boes="2.0.0">
    <name>Za-Khazi Run, Center</name>
    <comment>Comment</comment>
    <encounter can-flee="false" force="true">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>128</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>12</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </encounter>
    <encounter can-flee="false" force="true">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>67</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </encounter>
    <wandering can-flee="false" force="false">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>67</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </wandering>
    <wandering can-flee="true" force="false">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>66</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </wandering>
    <wandering can-flee="false" force="false">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>65</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </wandering>
    <sign id="0">
        <![CDATA[REALM OF MOROG|Those not welcomed, beware!]]>
    </sign>
    <sign id="1">
        <![CDATA[Calamity]]>
    </sign>
    <sign id="7" />
    <area top="33" left="6" bottom="35" right="10">Misty Pools</area>
    <area top="13" left="42" bottom="21" right="44">Rocky Climb</area>
    <string id="0">
        <![CDATA[As you make your way down this winding path, you notice a glitter from the ground nearby. Looking closer, you find a small, round, iridescent gemstone. ]]>
    </string>
    <string id="6">
        <![CDATA[The cave path slopes sharply upward to the north. The ground is unusually rocky and uneven, even for these tunnels. It will take a while to reach the end.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="7">
        <![CDATA[You have made your way to the top of a large cliff. The stone surface is sheer, with very few footholds. A hundred feet below you, you can see a wide gallery, which looks somewhat familiar.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="8">
        <![CDATA[After a while, you come to the conclusion that you could probably climb down the cliff safely. However, you doubt you would be able to make it back up.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="13">
        <![CDATA[It takes a few hours, but by making makeshift ropes and working your way down extremely carefully, you finally manage to arrive safely at the bottom of the cliff.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="14">
        <![CDATA[Panting and wheezing, you finally reach the top of this long, rubble strewn gallery. Looking back, you don't relish the thought of climbing back down.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="15">
        <![CDATA[The last few hundred feet of the journey were the worst, not only because of fatigue but because all of the boulders were covered with a thin layer of frost. Once you reach the top, you look around to try and figure out why it's so cold here.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="16">
        <![CDATA[After a short search, you find a large cave entrance. The frost is thickest here, and icicles hang from the stone above your heads.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="20">
        <![CDATA[Being careful not to slip on the ice, you make your way into the tunnel. It goes for about a hundred feet and then opens into a large, beautiful, frozen cavern.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="21">
        <![CDATA[The walls, floor, and ceiling are covered with sheets of ice. It reflects you, and reflects your reflections, showing your group back to you from an infinite variety of angles.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="22">
        <![CDATA[Soon, however, the reflections of other forms mingle with yours. The ice on what at first appeared to be boulders cracks, revealing large, blue lizards. They were sleeping, until your arrival disturbed them. Now awake, they are very hungry.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="26">
        <![CDATA[The drakes had a good deal of treasure, although it takes a while to chip it out of the ice. There's a lot of gold, and a frozen giant lizard or two for food. While you aren't able to recover a few scrolls, there's also a nice wand.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="27">
        <![CDATA[Finally, below all of the gold and other loot, you eventually dig down to a large, bronze key. The handle end is worked into the shape of a dragon's head.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="28">
        <![CDATA[You have passed from beauty into darkness. The loveliness of the unicorn's caverns are only a memory. Now, you look out over a desolate landscape of stagnant pools, scattered bones, and sharp rubble.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="29">
        <![CDATA[This enormous cavern is cold and dim, and you can make out stooped, shambling shapes making their way through the grim landscape.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="30">
        <![CDATA[As you walk among these algae-choked pools, you notice that the mist suspended above them has started to move towards you. Soon, it takes a more solid form. Insubstantial creatures hover around you. You shiver inside your armor.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="31">
        <![CDATA[The creatures whisper amongst themselves, seemingly unsure what to do with you. The whispers are so faint and fleeting that you can neither tell what they are saying nor even tell who is speaking.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="32">
        <![CDATA[Finally, one of them says, in a flat, hostile voice, "What is the word of safe passage?"]]>
    </string>
    <string id="36">
        <![CDATA[One at a time, they all whisper "Wrong." They then charge you, hoping to feed to feed on your still living flesh.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="37">
        <![CDATA[When you say the word, the beings flinch back, as if struck. Then, disappointed, they float back out over the pools, and again take on the appearance of harmless mist.]]>
    </string>
</sector>
