<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<sector boes="2.0.0">
    <name>Za-Khazi Run, South Tip</name>
    <comment>Comment</comment>
    <encounter can-flee="false" force="true">
        <monster>120</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>10</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </encounter>
    <wandering can-flee="true" force="false">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>73</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </wandering>
    <wandering can-flee="true" force="false">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>178</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </wandering>
    <sign id="0">
        <![CDATA[(The obelisk is ancient and well worn. You are only able to make out one word.)|Za-Khazi]]>
    </sign>
    <area top="37" left="17" bottom="40" right="21">Near Fort Goodling</area>
    <area top="11" left="24" bottom="18" right="28">Set of Falls</area>
    <string id="0">
        <![CDATA[To the west, the river becomes too rough and fast to row against. It looks like you have no choice but to continue down the Za-Khazi Run, to the east.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="1">
        <![CDATA[You row your boat out onto the river, moving downriver to the east into the Za-Khazi run. It's reputed to be 200 miles of the most unpleasant, savage, untamed caverns in all of Exile.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="2">
        <![CDATA[It's between you and your goal, and you have only 21 days to get through it. Normally, it would be no problem to move two hundred miles in three weeks, but not when you're heading into unknown caves, filled with all manner of monsters.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="3">
        <![CDATA[Of course, it may be just an easy simple boat trip, over in 2 days. There's only one way to find out ...]]>
    </string>
    <string id="4">
        <![CDATA[(You can see how many days have passed in the top right panel, next to your gold.)]]>
    </string>
    <string id="7">
        <![CDATA[The river so far is calm and peaceful, and, in fact, quite pleasant. The cave ceiling is covered with the glowing green fungus common in Exile, and covers the water with a soft light. Small flecks of mica in the wall catch the light. It's quite lovely.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="8">
        <![CDATA[This trip may not be bad after all. Just a relaxing vacation.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="13">
        <![CDATA[On the shore of the river, you find the wreck of a small cavewood rowboat, remarkably similar to the one you're using. It looks like the bottom was torn out by one of the many sharp rocks just under the water surface.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="14">
        <![CDATA[There are no bodies, though. You do, however, find tracks leading to the north.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="15">
        <![CDATA[You find a cold campsite, with several crude stone cairns nearby. A band of Exile soldiers, stranded here, starved to death. The final survivor covered the bodies of the others with stone and then died himself.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="16">
        <![CDATA[The survivor's armor and weapons have corroded, but you notice a ring on its skeletal finger. You can take it with you, if you're comfortable robbing the dead.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="21">
        <![CDATA[You help yourself to the ring and cover the body with a few stones. There's nothing left to do here. You leave this depressing scene behind.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="22">
        <![CDATA[The peaceful ride is about to come to an end. When people told you about the Za-Khazi Run, they mentioned nothing about the rapids.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="23">
        <![CDATA[And yet, here they are. Rough, fast, and dangerous looking. Worse, there are no portages, and the water is far too fast to row against. If you go through these rapids, there is no guarantee that you will be able to go back.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="24">
        <![CDATA[It looks like the adventure is truly about to begin.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="28">
        <![CDATA[You made it through the rapids safely, but now there's no going back. Welcome to the Za-Khazi Run.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="29">
        <![CDATA[This arm of the river ends in a dead end. There's a small patch of uninteresting land to the west. You've lost some valuable time.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="30">
        <![CDATA[This quiet, peaceful beach has suddenly become active with activity. A pile of small, chattering blue creatures just came out of nowhere, jumping up and down, baring small fangs, and running hungrily towards you.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="31">
        <![CDATA[This must be the Run's welcoming committee.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="32">
        <![CDATA[Searching the gremlins, you're able to find some grubby (but still edible) food. Waste not, want not.]]>
    </string>
</sector>
