<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<!-- NOTE: This file should be updated to use relative positioning the next time it changes. -->
<?xml-stylesheet href="dialog.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<dialog defbtn='okay' escbtn='okay'>
	<!--
	 TODO: This dialog is very disorganized; clean it up
	 -->
	<pict type='dlog' num='24' top='6' left='6'/>
	<text top='6' left='50' width='235' height='16'>BLADES OF EXILE HELP: MAGIC</text>
	<text top='23' left='60' width='427' height='32'>
		There are two sorts of magic spells:
		mage spells and priest spells.
		There are 62 spells of each type,
		each with a level from one to seven.
	</text>
	<text top='52' left='60' width='420' height='28'>
		You can only cast mage (or priest) spells of a level as high as your Mage (or Priest) Spells skill.
		There are two ways to cast a spell:
	</text>
	<text top='277' left='60' width='438' height='54'>
		Mage spells cannot be cast by someone wearing bulky armor
		(although armor can be put on after you're through casting spells).
		<br/>
		WARNING: Spells cast by a PC with 1, 2 or 3 intelligence will be very weak!
	</text>
	<text top='235' left='60' width='438' height='41'>
		You start automatically knowing most spells up to level 3.
		Other spells you have to track down.
		Some are known by sages who can teach them to you (for a price).
		Others must be found in dungeons and ruins.
	</text>
	<text top='193' left='60' width='436' height='41'>
		When you decide to cast a spell,
		you will be a given a list of spells with green lights
		next to the spells you are currently able to cast
		(and not those that you are, say, too low a level to cast).
	</text>
	<text top='332' left='60' width='440' height='54'>
		Note that spell effects are cumulative.
		Two poison spells do more than twice the damage of one poison spell.
		If a fear spell doesn't work, the next one will be more likely to.
		Casting 3 bless spells on a PC will make them a powerhouse.
	</text>
	<text top='81' left='77' width='397' height='54'>
		SPELL MENUS -
		The Cast Mage and Cast Priest menus are automatically updated to contain the spells the active PC can cast.
		To have a PC cast a spell, click on that PC's name to the upper right,
		and select the spell to cast from these menus.
	</text>
	<text top='136' left='77' width='398' height='54'>
		SPELL CASTING WINDOW -
		Press the mage or priest spell button to the lower left (or type 'm' or 'p').
		Press the number of the character to cast, the button by the spell,
		and then the target button by the PC to cast the spell on (if needed).
	</text>
	<button name='okay' type='regular' top='391' left='441'>OK</button>
</dialog>
