<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<dialogue boes="2.0.0">
    <personality id="190">
        <title>Gliak</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[There is a Vahnatai warrior sitting behind the stone table, hard at work carefully sharpening one of their long, wavy blades. He gives you a cold look when you approach.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["I am being Gliak."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["I am fighting warrior.  I do not wish with you talking, but Zoat-Ihrno commands me so."]]>
        </job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="191">
        <title>Iglit</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[This Vahnatai has the dull eyes and chalky, dry skin that afflicts these creatures in old age. She seems lost in thought.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA[You startle her from her reverie. "Oh, forgiveness asking. I am Iglit."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA[She forces herself to look up at you. "I am a ponder."]]>
        </job>
        <unknown>
            <![CDATA["Forgivenss. I not understand."]]>
        </unknown>
    </personality>
    <personality id="192">
        <title>Stal</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[You meet an exceptionally tall Vahnatai, so thin you're amazed it can walk. When you entered, it was writing something in a stylus on a clay tablet.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["I Stal. Welcome." His competence with your tongue seems limited.]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["Ponder. I ponder."]]>
        </job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="193">
        <title>Zoat-Ihrno</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[The fort's commander sits in his office, waiting for your appearance. He stands, bows to you, and sits again.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["I am Zoat-Ihrno. Welcome."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["I am commander of this fortress. I wanted to speak with you about your reason for appearing."]]>
        </job>
        <unknown>
            <![CDATA["Apologies. I do not understand."]]>
        </unknown>
    </personality>
    <personality id="194">
        <title>Presso-Bok</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[You arrive in the presence of another Crystal Soul. It is very different from being near Casser-Bok. It's a lot more peaceful. The sense of menace and agitation is not present.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA[You hear its gentle voice in your mind. "I am Presso-Bok."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["I can speak little with you of my task. It is private. I must instead speak with you of the matter of Casser-Bok."]]>
        </job>
        <unknown>
            <![CDATA[You sense confusion.]]>
        </unknown>
    </personality>
    <personality id="195">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="196">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="197">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="198">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="199">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <node for="190">
        <keyword>figh</keyword>
        <keyword>warr</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I am of a long line of bold fighters. Many of our line were slain by humans."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="190">
        <keyword>slai</keyword>
        <keyword>huma</keyword>
        <type>end-force</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Many of us fought on the surface to avenge our people against the Empire. You humans slew most of them. Others forgive. I will not. I will not help you." He turns away.]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="190">
        <keyword>zoat</keyword>
        <keyword>comm</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Zoat-Ihrno is being my commander, but though he thinking humans safe to be dealing with, I not forget many of us slain by you."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="191">
        <keyword>pond</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Though I am of age and seem distracted, I think much of things that are happening. That is the job of a ponder, to think and contemplate and advise. This is of great importance, here at this outpost."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="191">
        <keyword>outp</keyword>
        <keyword>impo</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["We are here to watch going on in Exile's war, and be reporting the news back to our people. I look at the information, sort it, and find what is worth telling back to them, with analyzing."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["But that is not important. Our commander has asked me to assist you."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="191">
        <keyword>comm</keyword>
        <keyword>assi</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Zoat-Ihrno has asked me to help you. We Vahnatai always like surface supplies. You can sell things to me. Also, I can identify, if you wish."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="191">
        <keyword>sell</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>sell-any</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[She looks through your inventory and makes an offer on every identified item.]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="191">
        <keyword>purc</keyword>
        <keyword>iden</keyword>
        <type>id</type>
        <param>20</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[She looks at each of your items and mumbles a brief spell. "I know what all your things are being. For 20 gold each, I can say what they are."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="192">
        <keyword>pond</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Ponder think. Guide. Help to people. I plan outpost seeking."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="192">
        <keyword>outp</keyword>
        <keyword>seek</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Outpost here seek know on human slith war. I guide where look talk think. You know. Also, I teach to people here."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="192">
        <keyword>teac</keyword>
        <keyword>peop</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I train. Command say me you train if can. I speak bad teach good. You me train?"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="192">
        <keyword>trai</keyword>
        <keyword>purc</keyword>
        <type>train</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text />
    </node>
    <node for="193">
        <keyword>comm</keyword>
        <keyword>fort</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["You humans should not be concerned about this outpost. We are not here to spy, but to observe. A subtle difference. We are watching your war, and reporting back all the things that are publicly known. We mean you no ill."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I wished to speak with you of your reason for appearing here."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="193">
        <keyword>reas</keyword>
        <keyword>appe</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["You said that you brought a message from Casser-Bok. That is the last thing we were expecting. We could have dealt with or ignored you on our own terms, but for that. This is larger, so you must take the message to our secret leader."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="193">
        <keyword>secr</keyword>
        <keyword>lead</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["The slith and human war is important to us. This outpost is an important tool for watching it. Thus, we have been given the greatest honor. A crystal soul is here, to give us guidance."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="193">
        <keyword>crys</keyword>
        <keyword>soul</keyword>
        <type>if-sdf</type>
        <param>190</param>
        <param>7</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["One of our greatest treasures is here to guide us in our watching. It is Presso-Bok. It wishes to see you. Say the word, and I will open the gate."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Now that you have your response to Casser-Bok, our crystal soul no longer wishes to speak with you. It is done."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="193">
        <keyword>open</keyword>
        <keyword>gate</keyword>
        <type>call-local</type>
        <param>16</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text />
    </node>
    <node for="193">
        <keyword>slit</keyword>
        <keyword>huma</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Many of our leaders hate you humans beyond words, after you prevented our revenge against the Empire for its stealing several crystal souls from us. But I have met humans, and I do not think they are so terrible in their hearts."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["But I am but a soldier. That is not my thing to speak on."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="194">
        <keyword>task</keyword>
        <keyword>priv</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I do not care for humans, and have little wish to give them aid I do not need to. We Crystal Souls have had a difficult history with humans."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="194">
        <keyword>diff</keyword>
        <keyword>huma</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["When we first met humans, some Empire humans stole several Crystal Souls and submitted them to horrible tortures. Since then, humans have been suspect. If not deserving of loathing."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="194">
        <keyword>matt</keyword>
        <keyword>cass</keyword>
        <type>set-sdf</type>
        <param>17</param>
        <param>7</param>
        <param>1</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Casser-Bok sent you here to tell us he wishes to return to his people. Is this correct?" You say that it is. "I must tell you that our response is no. It may never return. The tale of Casser-Bok is a horrible one."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="194">
        <keyword>tale</keyword>
        <keyword>horr</keyword>
        <type>set-sdf</type>
        <param>19</param>
        <param>7</param>
        <param>1</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["When a Vahnatai of great value and knowledge dies, the Vahnatai seekers turn the valued one's spirit into a Crystal Soul, like myself, to forever guide and provide wisdom to our people."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Sometimes, however, this does not happen smoothly."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="194">
        <keyword>happ</keyword>
        <keyword>smoo</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Sometimes, a Vahnatai wants to become a Crystal Soul, but it not chosen. One such being exists in undead state in a tower crypt to the south. Other times, the ritual of transformation is a failure. These times are very tragic."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Finally, sometimes a Crystal Soul does not adjust well to solid form. Flaws in the personality come forth."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="194">
        <keyword>flaw</keyword>
        <keyword>pers</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Casser-Bok is such a case. He is mad. He did not wish to guide, but to rule. He did not listen to requests, but gave orders. And when he was not obeyed, he murdered several Vahnatai."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="194">
        <keyword>murd</keyword>
        <keyword>seve</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["These murders were shocking and unforgivable, but destroying a Crystal Soul is against our nature. So we banished him. He has been trying to return ever since, but has also slain any Vahnatai that came within its reach."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I have advice for you. Serious advice."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="194">
        <keyword>serv</keyword>
        <keyword>advi</keyword>
        <type>set-sdf</type>
        <param>17</param>
        <param>7</param>
        <param>1</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["You can go back to Casser-Bok to give my message now, but I advise against it. He is mad, and may harm you when his request is refused. That is all."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
</dialogue>
