<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<dialogue boes="2.0.0">
    <personality id="210">
        <title>Commander Malak</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[You doubt you've ever met a person who looked so thankful to see you. When you enter his chambers, Commander Malak leaps to his feet to shake your hand. The last few weeks have been hard on him. He's probably about 30, but looks much older.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["I am Commander Malak. I could not be more pleased to meet you."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["I'm leading the defense of Fort Cavalier against the sliths. Thanks to you and the wands, we actually have hope now."]]>
        </job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="211">
        <title>Janis</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[You meet a tired looking priestess. She's patrolling the fort, looking for someone who's been wounded. When she sees you, however, she runs up to you, pleased to meet the saviors of Fort Cavalier.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["I am Janis. Mother Janis. Welcome."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["I do healing for this fortress. I'm required to charge for healing for visitors, but I can give you a very reasonable rate if you're ill."]]>
        </job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="212">
        <title>Silver</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[You meet the fort's quartermaster. You don't expect to meet people this old at the front. His armor is weighing him down, and he looks very tired.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["The folks here call me Silver. On account of the color of the hair I got left."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["I look after the supplies we got. What little we got. And I obtain newer stuff when I can."]]>
        </job>
        <unknown>
            <![CDATA["Sorry? What?"]]>
        </unknown>
    </personality>
    <personality id="213">
        <title>Veronica</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[This dangerous looking woman is pacing around the dining hall, reading a spell book and memorizing spells. When she sees you, however, she smiles and bows. Looks like you're finally getting some respect.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["I am Veronica. Respects to you."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["I am Fort Cavalier's mage. Its only mage."]]>
        </job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="214">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="215">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="216">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="217">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="218">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="219">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <node for="210">
        <keyword>slit</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Don't get me wrong. I actually have no problem with the slithzerikai in general. Several of them fought by my side during the war with the Empire. Nobler warriors I've never had the honor of fighting with."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="210">
        <keyword>fort</keyword>
        <keyword>cava</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He grins. "It's a rough place, built in haste, with half the fighters it should have. Yet, we've held up half of the slith army for months. How about that?"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="210">
        <keyword>wand</keyword>
        <keyword>hope</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["There ware fifteen wands, all strong. Fireblasts, shockstorms, one for charming, and all with extra charges. Used carefully, they'll keep us going for weeks." ]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He laughs. "That reminds me, you deserve to be rewarded. And you probably want to return to Exile."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="210">
        <keyword>retu</keyword>
        <keyword>exil</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["This fort has a concealed tunnel leading out. It's in a shed at the east side. Go out through there." From there, he gives you instructions to get back to civilization.]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="210">
        <keyword>dese</keyword>
        <keyword>rewa</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["You'll get your gold when you return to Exile. Also, be sure to speak with people around the fort. Many of them are very eager to help you." He points at the chest near his desk.]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["We also have something extra for you in there."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="210">
        <keyword>defe</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Sieges are long, bloody work. We killed ten of them for every one of us we lost, and losing because of it."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="211">
        <keyword>heal</keyword>
        <keyword>purc</keyword>
        <type>shop</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>5</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[Janis the Healer]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="212">
        <keyword>supp</keyword>
        <keyword>litt</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["We been conserving all of our stuff during this siege, but things are getting low. The wands you brought us should make all the difference. Thanks."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="212">
        <keyword>obta</keyword>
        <keyword>newe</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Yeah. You can sell me things. I got money that the commander gave me to buy us new stuff. And if you don't know what your things are, I can identify them. I been doing this so long, I can tell what about anything is."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="212">
        <keyword>iden</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>id</type>
        <param>2</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He looks over your supplies, and says "I'll tell you what all your stuff is. Only two gold each. For my trouble."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="212">
        <keyword>sell</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>sell-any</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[Silver looks over your supplies and makes an offer for everything identified.]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="213">
        <keyword>only</keyword>
        <keyword>mage</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["That's one of the reasons why we've had so much trouble defending the fort, and why we needed the wands you sent so badly. If we wanted a fireball, I had to cast it, and I can only do that so many times in a day."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["By the way, in return for your help, there's a spell I would like to teach you."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="213">
        <keyword>spel</keyword>
        <keyword>teac</keyword>
        <type>call-local</type>
        <param>12</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text />
    </node>
    <node for="213">
        <keyword>wand</keyword>
        <keyword>fire</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["We were about to get two more mages. Then the siege hit. Cut off, we were stuck with minimal magical support. Magic can't be more important when defending a place like this."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="211">
        <keyword>reas</keyword>
        <keyword>rate</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["It seems terrible, I'm sure, charging for healing. However, we have to, if we're going to get supplies."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="211">
        <keyword>supp</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[She chuckles dryly. "Since Exile can't get supplies to us, we have to sneak groups out through the secret exit and buy supplies from passing Nephilim and other creatures. Painful situation. I wish I could have stayed a teacher."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="211">
        <keyword>secr</keyword>
        <keyword>exit</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Commander Malak can tell you more about that. His office is in the southwest corner."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="211">
        <keyword>teac</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>call-local</type>
        <param>13</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["You're interested? Come with me." She pulls you aside and explains a remarkable ritual to you. You can now cast the spell Wall of Blades.]]>
        </text>
    </node>
</dialogue>
