<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<dialogue boes="2.0.0">
    <personality id="170">
        <title>Casser-Bok</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[You come face to face with Casser-Bok. It is a beautiful, flawless blue crystal, about eighteen inches long. Brief flashes of light and energy bounce back and forth inside it. You think you can see that it's vibrating slightly.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA[Its voice sounds out inside your mind. You hear its words as if they were your own thoughts. It's quite disconcerting. "Welcome. I am Casser-Bok."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["I spend my years here, living in quiet contemplation."]]>
        </job>
        <unknown>
            <![CDATA[Casser-Bok projects a feeling of confusion into your mind.]]>
        </unknown>
    </personality>
    <personality id="171">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="172">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="173">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="174">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="175">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="176">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="177">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="178">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="179">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>spen</keyword>
        <keyword>year</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["My life in my blessed form has been a long one, and will be longer still. In this form, I can see stars being born and dying, and watch the continents march about this sphere." What an odd thing to say. It makes little sense to you.]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>marc</keyword>
        <keyword>sphe</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Never mind that. It is valuable knowledge, but not of interest to the likes of you."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>quie</keyword>
        <keyword>cont</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Why else would the living Vahnatai have remade me in this form, except to think for them and to serve them and obey them in their wishes?" You detect a slight agitation in the mental voice. It makes your head hurt slightly.]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["But no matter. You are in my presence now, and I am glad."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>livi</keyword>
        <keyword>vahn</keyword>
        <type>if-sdf</type>
        <param>17</param>
        <param>2</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["The living Vahnatai use my superior kind as storehouses of knowledge. To aid them. To serve them."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Curse the Vahnatai! It is they who should serve us! Not the other way around! They will bow to us, or we will avenge ourselves upon them! Damn them all!" You stagger back under the force of the words.]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>thin</keyword>
        <keyword>serv</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Once, I was a mighty warlord for the Vahnatai. Then I died, and was remade in this form."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>rema</keyword>
        <keyword>form</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I was a great warlord, and won many victories, but was then remade in this form, to sit and obey orders instead of give them. There were disagreements. Difficulties. That is why I am glad you are here. Glad."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>disa</keyword>
        <keyword>diff</keyword>
        <type>if-sdf</type>
        <param>17</param>
        <param>2</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[A raspy chuckle saws through your mind. "Not all beings can always agree with all beings. That is why I decided to live apart from my people for a while, in order to rethink my place among them. That is why I wished your presence."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["The fools did not obey me! I could have lead them to greatness, but they were determined to only listen. So they trapped me here! But I will return one day! I will, and they will pay!"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>glad</keyword>
        <keyword>pres</keyword>
        <type>if-sdf</type>
        <param>17</param>
        <param>2</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["My agents have followed your progress through the caves with great interest. You have been very useful to others. I have a mission I wish to give you. Complete it, and you will be rewarded."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I am glad, because now I can take my fury out upon you. It is a therapeutic release. You can take the northern portal to try to recover the Crystal of Purity. Do not expect to reach it alive."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>miss</keyword>
        <keyword>rewa</keyword>
        <type>call-local</type>
        <param>49</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["You have done all you can for me, fool. Now enter the northern portal to try to recover your reward." The hostility in the voice in your mind makes you break out in a sweat.]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>crys</keyword>
        <keyword>puri</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["The Crystal of Purity is a valuable artifact for magical research. Very valuable. You should be honored I would ever think of giving you such a thing."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>outp</keyword>
        <keyword>hidd</keyword>
        <type>call-local</type>
        <param>59</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["The outpost is hidden some miles to the north, to the west of a lair of troglodytes. Look for a cavern filled with large worms. Their outpost is hidden beyond them. Say you come from me, and they are sure to speak with you."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[(You can now find the Vahnatai outpost.)]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>agen</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Let us not speak of that. I choose to keep aware of what happens in these caverns. That is all."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>resp</keyword>
        <keyword>dese</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Ah, but I wish you could have seen the victories I won for them. I am a mighty warlord."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>mess</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I have not been near my people for many years. I feel they are now ready to give me the respect I deserve."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
</dialogue>
