<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<town boes="2.0.0">
    <size>48</size>
    <name>Lair of Casser-Bok</name>
    <comment>Comment 1</comment>
    <comment>Comment 2</comment>
    <comment>Comment 3</comment>
    <bounds top="0" left="0" bottom="47" right="44" />
    <difficulty>6</difficulty>
    <lighting>dark</lighting>
    <flags>
        <chop kills="30000" />
    </flags>
    <item id="0">
        <type>30</type>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="1">
        <type>30</type>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="2">
        <type>30</type>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="3">
        <type>30</type>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="4">
        <type>30</type>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="5">
        <type>96</type>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="6">
        <type>17</type>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="7">
        <type>17</type>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="8">
        <type>222</type>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="9">
        <type>222</type>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="10">
        <type>222</type>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="11">
        <type>30</type>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="12">
        <type>30</type>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="13">
        <type>96</type>
        <property>true</property>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="14">
        <type>96</type>
        <property>true</property>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="15">
        <type>93</type>
        <property>true</property>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="16">
        <type>93</type>
        <property>true</property>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="17">
        <type>24</type>
    </item>
    <item id="18">
        <type>24</type>
    </item>
    <item id="19">
        <type>0</type>
        <charges>49</charges>
    </item>
    <item id="20">
        <type>116</type>
    </item>
    <item id="21">
        <type>350</type>
    </item>
    <item id="22">
        <type>18</type>
    </item>
    <item id="23">
        <type>30</type>
    </item>
    <item id="24">
        <type>30</type>
    </item>
    <item id="25">
        <type>96</type>
        <charges>2</charges>
    </item>
    <item id="26">
        <type>30</type>
    </item>
    <item id="27">
        <type>30</type>
    </item>
    <item id="28">
        <type>222</type>
    </item>
    <item id="29">
        <type>222</type>
    </item>
    <item id="30">
        <type>0</type>
        <charges>68</charges>
    </item>
    <item id="31">
        <type>186</type>
    </item>
    <item id="32">
        <type>23</type>
    </item>
    <creature id="0">
        <type>107</type>
        <attitude>docile</attitude>
        <mobility>0</mobility>
        <personality>170</personality>
        <face>25</face>
        <onkill>16</onkill>
    </creature>
    <creature id="1">
        <type>134</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>1</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>-1</face>
    </creature>
    <creature id="2">
        <type>134</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>1</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>-1</face>
    </creature>
    <creature id="3">
        <type>134</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>1</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>-1</face>
    </creature>
    <creature id="4">
        <type>134</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>1</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>-1</face>
    </creature>
    <creature id="5">
        <type>134</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>1</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>-1</face>
    </creature>
    <creature id="6">
        <type>71</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>1</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>-1</face>
        <encounter>1</encounter>
    </creature>
    <creature id="7">
        <type>71</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>1</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>-1</face>
        <encounter>1</encounter>
    </creature>
    <creature id="8">
        <type>71</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>1</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>-1</face>
        <encounter>1</encounter>
    </creature>
    <creature id="9">
        <type>196</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>0</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>-1</face>
    </creature>
    <creature id="10">
        <type>196</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>0</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>-1</face>
    </creature>
    <creature id="11">
        <type>196</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>0</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>-1</face>
    </creature>
    <creature id="12">
        <type>196</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>0</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>-1</face>
    </creature>
    <creature id="13">
        <type>196</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>0</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>-1</face>
    </creature>
    <area top="38" left="2" bottom="46" right="14">Casser-Bok&apos;s Chamber</area>
    <area top="30" left="2" bottom="36" right="6">Reading Room</area>
    <area top="1" left="1" bottom="17" right="24">Cavern of Many Paths</area>
    <area top="38" left="29" bottom="46" right="37">Entry Hall</area>
    <area top="31" left="37" bottom="36" right="41">Treasure Room</area>
    <area top="21" left="31" bottom="27" right="43">Portcullis Puzzle</area>
    <area top="4" left="28" bottom="16" right="40">Searing &#x0D;Searing Maze</area>
    <area top="19" left="2" bottom="28" right="18">Filth Pit</area>
    <area top="18" left="22" bottom="29" right="30">Charnel House</area>
    <sign id="0">
        <![CDATA[Enter to Meet the Mighty Casser-Bok]]>
    </sign>
    <sign id="1">
        <![CDATA[Only One May Approach the Majesty|Enter portal to be blessed.]]>
    </sign>
    <sign id="2">
        <![CDATA[Cloak Check]]>
    </sign>
    <sign id="3">
        <![CDATA[Cloak Check]]>
    </sign>
    <sign id="4">
        <![CDATA[To the Chambers of the Crystals]]>
    </sign>
    <string id="0">
        <![CDATA[Click.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="1">
        <![CDATA[Clang.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="2">
        <![CDATA[Your final blow shatters Casser-Bok. As the shards fly across the room, a spirit rises from the fragments, floats up to the ceiling, and disappears. As you watch it rise, its final trap roars into action.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="3">
        <![CDATA[Quickfire appears all throughout the crypt. The portals you counted on for your escape disappear. The crypt entrance caves in, making escape impossible. All of this happens in the span of moments. You're trapped inside, and burn up.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="4">
        <![CDATA[You enter the hall of Casser-Bok. He (or she, or it) is a Crystal Soul. These are the most sacred beings of the Vahnatai people, their Gods, for all practical purposes. They are the physical form of the spirits of their most valued ancestors.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="5">
        <![CDATA[Normally, they are kept at the heart of Vahnatai lands, in order to to protect them from all harm. Yet, this Crystal Soul is here, far away from Vahnatai lands, isolated in this chilly tomb.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="6">
        <![CDATA[This treatment would normally be unthinkable to the Vahnatai. You wonder why it's out here.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="7">
        <![CDATA[You hear a gentle voice in your head, making itself felt inside your mind. The crystal soul says "I am Casser-Bok. Welcome to my home. Please, approach my glory."]]>
    </string>
    <string id="10">
        <![CDATA[When you approach the portal, a strange force holds you back. You try to get close to it, but invisible hands hold you away. Casser-Bok no longer wants your company.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="11">
        <![CDATA[When you try to get close to this portal, you find that only the nearest person can approach unimpeded. Everyone else in your group is held back by invisible hands.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="12">
        <![CDATA[A little experimentation reveals that the portal will only let one of you close to it. Whoever enters this place will have to do so alone.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="17">
        <![CDATA[One of you steps inside the portal. There is a brief moment of vertigo, and you find yourself in a different place.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="18">
        <![CDATA[You try to enter the portal to escape from the now erratic crystal soul. Unfortunately, you don't get within ten feet of it. Whenever you get close, an invisible force strikes you in the chest and throws you back.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="19">
        <![CDATA[You'll have to find another way out.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="20">
        <![CDATA[This portal has been placed here to reunite you with your party, if you're done here for now.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="26">
        <![CDATA[When you step on this rune, your lips feel slightly numb for a moment. Nothing else happens.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="27">
        <![CDATA[The Vahnatai rely on crystals for their needs as much as possible. For example, crystals such as this are used as magical books. Peering into one and concentrating, you can see words move slowly by for you to read.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="28">
        <![CDATA[This crystal looks very dark and old. You suspect that the magic of such stones fades with time, and this one has probably been here for centuries. Still, you might be able to read something inside it.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="33">
        <![CDATA[You stare into the murky depths of the stone until you give yourself a mild headache. You can't make out anything.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="34">
        <![CDATA[At first, you think this crystal is dark and dead. Then, looking deep inside, you realize that magical formulae are scrolling by inside. You concentrate on them, trying to make some sense of them.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="35">
        <![CDATA[Unfortunately, it's to no avail. They're too alien, too confusing, and too dim. You leave the crystal behind, getting nothing for your troubles but a splitting headache.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="36">
        <![CDATA[At first, you think this crystal is dark and dead. Then, looking deep inside, you realize that magical formulae are scrolling by inside. You concentrate on them, trying to make some sense of them.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="37">
        <![CDATA[Fortunately, your massive knowledge of Mage Lore pays off. You manage to understand the spell the crystal is showing you. You can now cast Quickfire.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="38">
        <![CDATA[When you try to enter the portal, it disappears. When you back away, it reappears. Casser-Bok must want you to stay right here.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="39">
        <![CDATA[This cavern has a smooth, flat floor, with long, winding cobblestone walkways set into it. The walkways seem like sort of a waste of effort. Maybe they appealed to Casser-Bok's sense of aesthetics.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="40">
        <![CDATA[When you walk through the door, the first things you see are bones. Piles of them. They're very long and delicate, with large, rounded skulls with huge eye sockets. It doesn't take long to figure out what they are - Vahnatai remains.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="41">
        <![CDATA[Worse, they were clearly killed by violence. Some are scarred by fire. Others have been crushed by weapon blows. Casser-Bok must be even more mad than you thought ... he's been killing his own people.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="42">
        <![CDATA[You find yourself face to face with Casser-Bok's heavy squad. They're Vahnavoi. They're sort of like Vahnatai zombies, only much worse ...]]>
    </string>
    <string id="43">
        <![CDATA[You hear, echoing down the corridors, what sounds like a portcullis opening.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="44">
        <![CDATA[You hear what sounds like a gate slamming shut.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="45">
        <![CDATA[Finally, you reach your prize, the reward for all this pain and inconvenience. You open the box and find a quartz crystal, about as long as your hand.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="46">
        <![CDATA[At first, you're disappointed. It seems like nothing more than an ordinary rock. Then you pick it up and look through it. It's remarkable! When you peer through it, everything beyond is visible in incredibly clear detail.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="47">
        <![CDATA[Every mote of dust, every crack, every blemish in the stone walls becomes apparent to you. When light passes through the stone, it seems to come through brighter on the other side.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="48">
        <![CDATA[For an adventurer, this thing is not very useful. To a magical researcher, however, this crystal is quite a prize. ]]>
    </string>
    <string id="51">
        <![CDATA[At long last, you have reached the portal out of here. Looking through it, you can just make out your compatriots waiting on the other side. Do you rejoin them?]]>
    </string>
    <string id="57">
        <![CDATA["There is a Vahnatai outpost hidden to the north. I want you to take a message to them. I wish you to tell them I wish to rejoin my people. The outpost is hidden, but I can help you find it."]]>
    </string>
    <string id="58">
        <![CDATA["If you carry this message and return this response to me, I will give you the Crystal of Purity."]]>
    </string>
    <string id="59">
        <![CDATA["As I said, take my message to the Vahnatai outpost to the north, to the west of the troglodyte castle. Then return their response to me, and I will give you the Crystal of Purity." ]]>
    </string>
    <string id="60">
        <![CDATA[You tell Casser-Bok about the Vahnatai's rejection. The creature screams in fury! The force of its yell throws you to the floor. Then it speaks. "Fine, then. My return to glory must wait. One day, they will accept my rule! I am sure of it!"]]>
    </string>
    <string id="61">
        <![CDATA["For now, I owe you a reward. Fine. Enter the northern portal. But I doubt you will survive to reach it."]]>
    </string>
    <string id="62">
        <![CDATA[This portal has very little energy coursing through it. It isn't able to take you anywhere.]]>
    </string>
</town>
