<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<dialogue boes="2.0.0">
    <personality id="10">
        <title>Klivans</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[Even for inns frequented by sailors, the Sea Wurm Inn is a bit on the scruffy side. The bar maid is doing her best to fight the decay, but it's been a losing struggle for some time.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA[She grabs some mugs, expecting some heavy drink orders. "I'm Klivans. Welcome to the Sea Wurm Inn."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["Well, our beer is great. Only 5 gold a mug. We have a room free for only 6 gold. And, if you're planning to travel, we have some rations."]]>
        </job>
        <unknown>
            <![CDATA["Can't you see I'm busy?"]]>
        </unknown>
    </personality>
    <personality id="11">
        <title>Vonnegut</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[When you get close to this small man, he nervously motions you over to join him. As you sit, he takes a quick look around the room, paying close attention to the windows and doors. When he sees it's safe, he turns to you.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA[He asks for your letters of introduction and looks them over carefully. Satisfied, he says "I am Vonnegut, adventurers. Welcome to Morrow's Isle." He continues to keep an eye on the windows and doors.]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["Forgive my caution, but the Hill Runners have made all our lives dangerous. I am here to explain the reason you've been brought here."]]>
        </job>
        <unknown>
            <![CDATA["That doesn't seem too important."]]>
        </unknown>
    </personality>
    <personality id="12">
        <title>Belk</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[With the tanned skin, earring, and tattoos, you have little doubt that this man is a sailor. He's currently working on what must be one of many beers.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA[He grunts and belches. "I'm Belk," he says. "Sit down and join me." He waves unsteadily at a nearby stool.]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA[He barks out a laugh, with a little spittle in addition. "I'm a sailor. Or I'm retired. I'm not sure."]]>
        </job>
        <unknown>
            <![CDATA[He grunts and takes a swig of beer.]]>
        </unknown>
    </personality>
    <personality id="13">
        <title>Purdee</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[Behind the counter, you see Purdee, the elegant and pert owner of Purdee's Resort. She bows to you as you approach, and wipes clean the counters in front of where you sit.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["I am Purdee, and I run Purdee's Resort, the loveliest inn in all of Valorim."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["Well, when the captains want a good place to stay, they come here. Fine, private room, only 14 gold. Good solid meals for sale. And, of course, bottles of Morrow Isle's finest wines, only 12 gold!"]]>
        </job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="14">
        <title>Bearden</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[This man's clothes tell two stories. They are high quality, made of silk and velvet, but they're also torn and dirtied, as if their wearer has had a hard time of it. His shirt is also stained with some of the wine he's been drinking.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA[He motions for you to sit and pours you some wine. "Greetings, fellow victims. I'm Bearden."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["None, any more. I'm a victim, sure as I'm sitting here." He gulps down more wine.]]>
        </job>
        <unknown>
            <![CDATA["What?"]]>
        </unknown>
    </personality>
    <personality id="15">
        <title>Elinor</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[When you walk up to the counter, the woman behind it looks up at you. For a brief instant, you see the intense fatigue clouding her eyes. Then she jumps up, spry and alert, to bow to you.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["I am Elinor. I am the trainer for the city of Selathni."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["I'm a trainer. Come to me when you need learning."]]>
        </job>
        <unknown>
            <![CDATA[She shrugs.]]>
        </unknown>
    </personality>
    <personality id="16">
        <title>Haedrich</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[Weaponsmiths are always greatly in demand, especially on an island as tormented and violence wracked as this one. However, although business must be good, the smith looks very grim.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA[He extends a massive hand to you. "I'm Haedrich."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["We have all sort of weapons, which you can purchase. You'll need them."]]>
        </job>
        <unknown>
            <![CDATA[He wipes sweat off his brow, and looks confused.]]>
        </unknown>
    </personality>
    <personality id="17">
        <title>Iggers</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[Although this man is a blacksmith, currently working on a breastplate, he looks surprisingly calm and clean. You soon see why ... he mutters a spell, and his hammer starts to glow. After a few more strikes, he sets it down to turn to talk with you.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["I am Iggers. Welcome to my shop."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["Oh, I'm very versatile. Most of the reason for my success. I can identify your items, and then you can sell them to me. Or, if you wish, I can provide you with all manner of fine armor."]]>
        </job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="18">
        <title>Blue</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[This shop is where you can come to get all manner of missile weapons. The woman behind the counter looks up at you with alacrity, ready to spring into action to serve you.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["I'm known as Blue. Long story. Welcome to my archery shop."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["We have missiles, bows, and bolts. Which would you like?"]]>
        </job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="19">
        <title>Michael</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[This wealthy and clean looking young man is probably the son of one of the better off people in town. He's in his late teens, and moves with the calm and confidance of the upper class.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA[He nods in greeting, looking at your arms and armor with interest. "I am Michael."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["Oh, I am but pacing about our fine city." He waves at it. "Is it not lovely?"]]>
        </job>
    </personality>
    <node for="10">
        <keyword>plan</keyword>
        <keyword>trav</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Yeah, I've heard a lot about problems traveling on the Isle. Get a beer, and I'll tell you about it."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="10">
        <keyword>beer</keyword>
        <keyword>grea</keyword>
        <type>buy-info</type>
        <param>5</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[You get a few mugs of the Inn's beer. As expected, it's noxious stuff. As you choke it down, Klivans says "You look new here. Have you heard the Isle's been dangerous lately?"]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Sorry. It costs 5 gold."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="10">
        <keyword>dang</keyword>
        <keyword>late</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["The northwest corner is full of jumpy Empire soldiers. The northeast is full of Hill Runners. I'd suggest staying close to home until you know what you're doing."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="10">
        <keyword>room</keyword>
        <keyword>free</keyword>
        <type>inn</type>
        <param>6</param>
        <param>1</param>
        <param>37</param>
        <param>40</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[You are shown to a cramped room, containing 3 lumpy beds, an armada of bed bugs, and not much else. You've spent a hellish night.]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Sorry. It costs 6 gold."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="10">
        <keyword>purc</keyword>
        <keyword>rati</keyword>
        <type>shop</type>
        <param>5</param>
        <param>7</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[Sea Wurm Inn]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="11">
        <keyword>forg</keyword>
        <keyword>caut</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["If you knew more of the Hill Runner's techniques, you would understand. Aiding the Empire will, before long, result in a visit from them. A terminal visit, if you catch my meaning."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="11">
        <keyword>hill</keyword>
        <keyword>runn</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["They are the rebels, the violent raiders and murderers who have turned this Isle into a place of constant terror. They are the reason you have been brought here."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="11">
        <keyword>reas</keyword>
        <keyword>brou</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["The Hill Runners, led by their leader Stalker, have had great success in fighting the Empire on Morrow's Isle. You have been brought here to infiltrate them. I am not here to tell you how."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I am only here to tell you of your contact, and to provide information."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="11">
        <keyword>succ</keyword>
        <keyword>figh</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["We could crush Stalker and his minions easily enough, but we do not want to call a whole army here to deal with such a rabble. The Emperor wants this issue handled quietly."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="11">
        <keyword>stal</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Practically nothing is known of him. Or her. Stalker is completely ruthless and vicious, and a shrewd tactician as well. If you can infiltrate the Hill Runners, we might be able to find and eliminate this threat."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Fortunately for us all, Stalker has an opposite, our leader Jaen."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="11">
        <keyword>jaen</keyword>
        <keyword>oppo</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Jaen was sent here by the Empire to destroy Stalker. He is just as secretive, and just as shrewd and vicious. It is he who will be giving you your orders. I am here to tell you how to contact him."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="11">
        <keyword>info</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He points to a door in the southeast corner of the room. "In my room are two books. Read them, and you will learn much of Morrow's Isle, and of our situation."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="11">
        <keyword>infi</keyword>
        <keyword>cont</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["You are to go to Willow, to the east of here. Somewhere in Willow is a secret stairway down, which leads to where our leader Jaen will speak with you and give you your orders."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["He will tell you how to infiltrate the Hill Runners, and why. However, before you go, a serious warning."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="11">
        <keyword>seri</keyword>
        <keyword>warn</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Like all adventurers on the Isle, we are sure you will be contacted by the Hill Runners, so that you can help them with their sinister deeds. Do nothing for them until you have been to the contact point to clear things with Jaen."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["If you help Stalker without permission, you will be slain."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="11">
        <keyword>will</keyword>
        <keyword>secr</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Willow isn't far to the east. I'm not sure where the contact point is in the town. I've never been down there. But then, you're adventurers, used to poking your noses into places you aren't supposed to be. I'm sure you'll find it."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="12">
        <keyword>spit</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Oops." He wipes up the spittle with his sleeve. "Sorry."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="12">
        <keyword>sail</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Making goods runs to Morrow's Isle was a good bit of work. Safe. Lots to do. They pay well. I was all set to retire, but then all the troubles started."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="12">
        <keyword>reti</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Yeah!" He blows his nose on his sleeve. "Years of work, and I'm finally ready to settle down. Buy a farm. Drink. But then I get here, and there's all these troubles going on."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="12">
        <keyword>trou</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I get here, and within one day, one of these Hill Runners comes up to me!" You see the barkeep look over, uncomfortable at the mention of the Hill Runners. "They try to convert me!"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="12">
        <keyword>conv</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["They say, help us or we cut you down in your sleep. Then a soldier comes up to me next day, and says he has his eye on me cause I was seen talkin' to a Hill Runner!" He snorts. "This place is madness. I'm escaping!"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="12">
        <keyword>madn</keyword>
        <keyword>esca</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I'm going somewhere where people aren't getting killed everywhere and you can keep to yourself. Pretty reasonable, eh?" You have a hard time disagreeing.]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="13">
        <keyword>capt</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Selathni is Morrow Isle's main port. We get a lot of sailors here, and their captains. The sailors go to other, lesser places. The captains come here."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="13">
        <keyword>purc</keyword>
        <keyword>meal</keyword>
        <type>shop</type>
        <param>4</param>
        <param>8</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[Purdee's Resort]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="13">
        <keyword>priv</keyword>
        <keyword>room</keyword>
        <type>inn</type>
        <param>14</param>
        <param>3</param>
        <param>20</param>
        <param>10</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[You pay the hefty price and are shown to a neat, private room with a very comfortable bed. Your sleep is deep and restful.]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[She shakes her head. "Sorry, friend. No quality without money."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="13">
        <keyword>fine</keyword>
        <keyword>wine</keyword>
        <type>buy-info</type>
        <param>12</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[She brings you a bottle of delicious, carefully aged wine. As you sip, she mentions conspiratorially, "By the way, adventurers, are you interested in rumors? I'm heard interesting things about the Empire, and about some monsters."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[She frowns. "You don't expect wine for free, now, do you?"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="13">
        <keyword>empi</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["All the Empire folks are in a tizzy because some sort of auditor or judge or something is coming here to look over the Hill Runner situation. Keep your eyes open on the streets of Selathni. This certain someone may be here any day now."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="13">
        <keyword>mons</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Just between you, me, and these four walls, some people have seen ogres in the hills at the southwest corner of the Isle."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="14">
        <keyword>wine</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Good stuff! Hic!" He hiccups enthusiastically.]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="14">
        <keyword>vict</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Well, I'd be glad to tell you all about it." He starts to fall over, and then rights himself. "I was running a lumber mill, in the ruins of what was Fahl. But then it was destroyed."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="14">
        <keyword>lumb</keyword>
        <keyword>mill</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Beautiful place! The serfs sawed and processed thirty big logs a day! It was going to make me rich, but then it got destroyed."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="14">
        <keyword>ruin</keyword>
        <keyword>fahl</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Fahl is, or was, in the woods to the, ummm, the northeast of here." He thinks, confused. "That's right! The northeast! But then a Hill Rider, or whatever they're called, raid burnt it to the ground."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["The only thing I was able to save was my horses. Want some? You can purchase a set for only 400 gold."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="14">
        <keyword>dest</keyword>
        <keyword>rich</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["That lumber mill was my way to richness! Lord Volpe said so when he invited me here! We were going to turn this island into a paradise! But now I'm stuck out in the cold, and Volpe doesn't do anything to help."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="14">
        <keyword>lord</keyword>
        <keyword>volp</keyword>
        <type>end-force</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He starts to get woozy. "Volpe is the lord who brought us here. We run it all. He's making this island great. He's ... he's ..." With a loud, satisfying thunk, Bearden's head hits the table. He snores.]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="15">
        <keyword>lear</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Learning is good."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="15">
        <keyword>trai</keyword>
        <keyword>purc</keyword>
        <type>train</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text />
    </node>
    <node for="15">
        <keyword>sain</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[When you say the password, she slumps back into her chair. The fatigue you saw earlier is back in full force. "Thank goodness. I've been jumping at shadows waiting for you to get here. Things have been a nightmare here. Plenty of troubles."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["You want the mahogany chest, yes?"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="15">
        <keyword>maho</keyword>
        <keyword>ches</keyword>
        <type>if-sdf</type>
        <param>1</param>
        <param>6</param>
        <param>1</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["It's hidden behind a dresser in one of the houses in town. Break into the house with the crossed swords by the door, search the dresser, and you'll find it. Oh, and by the way, we've been doing a little espionage. You'll be able to get to Zaskiva now."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["You took the box. I only have one."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="15">
        <keyword>nigh</keyword>
        <keyword>trou</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["First, there was that Empire spy Vonnegut. We dealt with him. Now there's an investigator coming."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="15">
        <keyword>vonn</keyword>
        <keyword>deal</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[She smiles. "Let's just say he's looking at things from under 10 feet of water now."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="15">
        <keyword>inve</keyword>
        <keyword>comi</keyword>
        <type>if-time</type>
        <param>25</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["She's coming here soon to look into things. The closer investigators get to me, the worse things are. That's why I'm glad for a chance to hand off the chest!"]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["She's here now. She's always wandering the streets, poking into things! The closer investigators get to me, the worse things are. That's why I'm glad for a chance to hand off the chest!"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="16">
        <keyword>weap</keyword>
        <keyword>purc</keyword>
        <type>shop</type>
        <param>3</param>
        <param>9</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[Haedrich's Weaponry]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="16">
        <keyword>need</keyword>
        <keyword>them</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["There's no safety, with those Hill Runners about."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="16">
        <keyword>hill</keyword>
        <keyword>runn</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He shakes his head. "I'm not much on politics. I don't know who's doing what. Or why. I just know what happened to Charles."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="16">
        <keyword>char</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[His voice is grim. "He was my boy. He was in a caravan trip, going northwest to Zaskiva. Hill Runners ambushed it. Killed everyone. Not just guards. Everyone. Seems they were delivering weapons to the Empire garrison. My child was innocent."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="16">
        <keyword>chil</keyword>
        <keyword>inno</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He shakes his head. "I don't have any crying left in me. Or yelling. I just know that what's going on, it ain't right." He shrugs. "Want some weapons?"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="17">
        <keyword>purc</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He looks confused. "Do you wish to purchase identification or armor?"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="17">
        <keyword>iden</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>id</type>
        <param>12</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He smiles. "I have little doubt that I can identify anything you have. My price? A mere 12 gold."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="17">
        <keyword>armo</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>shop</type>
        <param>2</param>
        <param>10</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[Armor by Iggers]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="17">
        <keyword>sell</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>sell-any</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He looks over your inventory and promptly and cheerily gives you an offer for each identified item.]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="17">
        <keyword>vers</keyword>
        <keyword>succ</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He smiles, and gets a faraway look in his eyes. "Ah, yes. When Lord Volpe told me of the opportunities here, I was skeptical in the extreme. But when he told me how much wealth I could obtain by following him here, well, how could I resist?"]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Rest assured, Volpe is a great man."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="17">
        <keyword>lord</keyword>
        <keyword>volp</keyword>
        <type>if-sdf</type>
        <param>101</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["The Empire made a wise decision the day they made him lord of Morrow's Isle. He rules from Zaskiva, to the northwest, and every day he makes this isle a more profitable enterprise."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["It was a dark day for Morrow's Isle when Lord Volpe was murdered. He made this isle a more profitable enterprise than it had ever been before."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="18">
        <keyword>miss</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>shop</type>
        <param>3</param>
        <param>11</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[Blue's Missiles]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="18">
        <keyword>bows</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>shop</type>
        <param>2</param>
        <param>12</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[Blue's Bows]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="18">
        <keyword>bolt</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>shop</type>
        <param>4</param>
        <param>13</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[Blue's Bolts]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="18">
        <keyword>purc</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Missiles, bows, or bolts?"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="19">
        <keyword>city</keyword>
        <keyword>love</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[You look around at Selathni. It is indeed a beautiful city. Michael fingers the silk collar of his shirt. "I do not, I simply cannot understand why some malcontents would want to spoil it!"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="19">
        <keyword>malc</keyword>
        <keyword>spoi</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["But it's all right." He smiles. "Jaen will sort them out!"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="19">
        <keyword>jaen</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>end-force</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He looks embarrassed, as if he's been caught talking about something he shouldn't. "Umm ... sorry. Forget I said anything about Jaen. Have a lovely day. Goodbye." He wanders away.]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="14">
        <keyword>purc</keyword>
        <keyword>hors</keyword>
        <type>buy-horse</type>
        <param>400</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>2</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He takes your gold and, with some difficulty, counts it. "Great! The horses are in the stables, some of them will go with you now." He orders beer in celebration of his good fortune.]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He belches angrily. It's an ugly sound. "You want to rob a destitute man? My horses are 400 gold!"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="-2">
        <keyword>hill</keyword>
        <keyword>runn</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[You get an awkward silence in return. For some reason, this person doesn't want to discuss this topic here.]]>
        </text>
    </node>
</dialogue>
