<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<sector boes="2.0.0">
    <name>Swampy Area</name>
    <comment>Comment</comment>
    <encounter can-flee="false" force="true">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>181</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>180</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </encounter>
    <wandering can-flee="true" force="false">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>189</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </wandering>
    <wandering can-flee="true" force="false">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>189</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>133</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </wandering>
    <wandering can-flee="true" force="false">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>181</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </wandering>
    <string id="0">
        <![CDATA[Way out here, deep in the grim marshes, you find a small, sod hut. A thin wisp of smoke rises from its chimney. It's surrounded by herb gardens on all sides. The door is closed, but you could knock on it.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="6">
        <![CDATA[When you reach the door, you don't even have time to knock. The door flies open, and a withered, scowling crone peers out at you. She's ancient and twisted, and looks very dangerous.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="12">
        <![CDATA[You pull out your swords. She jumps back, startled. As you start to enter her hut, she casts a spell. The hut shimmers around you, and disappears.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="13">
        <![CDATA[As you stand alone in the fen, you hear a harsh, screeching voice coming from somewhere nearby: "You'll pay for your rudeness, children!"]]>
    </string>
    <string id="14">
        <![CDATA[Oh well. Her herb garden stayed behind. You're able to pick some useful alchemical ingredients.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="15">
        <![CDATA[When she sees that you don't intend to be rude, she smiles. Her teeth are a charming green color. She says "Come in, my children! Come in! It is so rare I have someone to share my skills with."]]>
    </string>
    <string id="16">
        <![CDATA[She sees your hesitance at entering her hovel, and shrugs. "Oh well. Just as easy out here. I'm known as Fallatina, or I was, before I came out here to spend time with my cauldron and my herbs."]]>
    </string>
    <string id="17">
        <![CDATA["Oh, the wonderful potions I can make! And I will share them with you, if you pay the price. Will you?"]]>
    </string>
    <string id="21">
        <![CDATA[You respectfully decline. The witch shakes her head. "Ah, children, you do not know when you have had a generous offer made. Oh, well. I don't plan to go anywhere. Come back anytime." She withdraws into her hut, and slams the door.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="22">
        <![CDATA[Swamp Brews]]>
    </string>
    <string id="23">
        <![CDATA[Deep in the swamp, you find a deep, dank cave, almost overgrown with roots and reeds. There are large lizard tracks and gnawed bones everywhere, and the area stinks of reptilian malice.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="29">
        <![CDATA[Deep in the swamp, you find a deep, dank cave, almost overgrown with roots and reeds. There are large lizard tracks and gnawed bones everywhere, and the area stinks of reptilian malice.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="35">
        <![CDATA[Sure enough, inside the cavern, you find one of the many predatory, unfriendly denizens of the swamp. Its many heads growl hungrily, and it lumbers towards you.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="36">
        <![CDATA[Sure enough, inside the cavern, you find one of the many predatory, unfriendly denizens of the swamp. Its many heads growl hungrily, and it lumbers towards you.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="37">
        <![CDATA[As you walk through the trees, you suddenly stub your toe. Looking down, you see a stone slab, partially concealed by brush. ]]>
    </string>
    <string id="38">
        <![CDATA[Clearing away the brush, you see that the stone reads "First Stone." Odd.]]>
    </string>
</sector>
