<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<sector boes="2.0.0">
    <name>Stalker&apos;s Realm</name>
    <comment>Comment</comment>
    <encounter can-flee="false" force="true">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>13</monster>
        <monster>14</monster>
        <monster>19</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>28</monster>
        <monster>191</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>13</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </encounter>
    <sign id="7" />
    <area top="9" left="25" bottom="18" right="35">Rebel Valley                 </area>
    <string id="0">
        <![CDATA[Someone shouts from the hills "Keep going! You're almost to someone who can help you along!" You look up, but can't see who yelled it.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="1">
        <![CDATA[You finally reach the highest valley in the mountains of Morrow's Isle. Here, you see arrayed before you the rebel army of Stalker.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="2">
        <![CDATA[It's surprisingly unimpressive. You see six camps, each with 50 or so people camped around it. They're mostly hill folk, rough and crude, with a few mages and Empire defectors thrown in. This is the lot that's held off the Empire, in all its might?]]>
    </string>
    <string id="3">
        <![CDATA[Apparently so. Stalker's stealth and viciousness, combined with the cunning of his troops and the defendability of these hills, have enabled him to succeed where so many others have failed. And you're about to meet him.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="4">
        <![CDATA[To the east you see a massive fort, built into the mountain slope. Stalker's fortress awaits.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="7">
        <![CDATA[Stalker's army spends its time living in small stone huts, each set circled around a  large bonfire. Dead goats and casks of ale are always handy. His troops are clearly a rowdy lot.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="8">
        <![CDATA[They're also friendly, and they've heard of you. When they see you, they invite you in to eat and drink with them.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="13">
        <![CDATA[They are clearly offended, and walk away. They don't even bother to say goodbye.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="14">
        <![CDATA[The rebels welcome you in, and, with many hearty slaps on the back, serve you up huge, steaming chunks of roast goat and mugs of ale. They have all sorts of stories of adventure for you, and want to hear your stories as well.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="15">
        <![CDATA[As you drink with them, you start to notice something unsettling. These folks seem friendly enough, but their stories are horrifying. They involve burned villages, ambushes that turn into massacres, and vile tortures inflicted on Empire troops.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="16">
        <![CDATA[They're cheery, and clearly are impressed by you, but you detect a subtle undercurrent of barely controlled, psychotic violence, always under the surface, always ready to tear loose.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="17">
        <![CDATA[There can't be more than 500 men and women camped in this valley. But they're the most terrifying people you've ever met. When the time comes and the feast ends, you're more than ready to move on.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="20">
        <![CDATA[You have another hearty meal with Stalker's men, with plenty of ale to chase it down. The food is still good, and they are still scary.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="21">
        <![CDATA[Suddenly, rebel troops are everywhere! They're jumping out of holes in the ground, running down the mountain side, and charging towards you from the hills ahead. Their weapons aren't out, but they don't look friendly either.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="22">
        <![CDATA[When they get close, you see that there actually aren't many of them. Only about 20. Not a large group. You're nervous at first, until you see that they are led by O' Grady, the man who sent you on your deadly mission to Zaskiva.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="23">
        <![CDATA[Your relief at seeing a familiar face is short lived. He looks at you with disgust, even loathing. The other Hill Runners look no friendlier.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="24">
        <![CDATA[O' Grady says "Stalker has given orders. You are to be welcomed into our ranks, and given a high position. Higher even than me! I am not fooled, though. I know the Empire contacted you! I know you were brought here to finish us off." ]]>
    </string>
    <string id="25">
        <![CDATA["Surrender now, and we will take you to a ship and send you away from here. Do not surrender, and you will die." The rebels put their hands on their blades. They mean it. Do you surrender?]]>
    </string>
    <string id="27">
        <![CDATA[You give up your weapons, and the Hill Runners tie you up and drag you into the hills. Once there, they do not hesitate to stab each of you in the heart and dump the bodies in a gully.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="28">
        <![CDATA["Fine!" O' Grady yells. "We'll do this the hard way!" The rebels shout, and charge.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="29">
        <![CDATA[You search O' Grady's body. You find a scroll, signed by Stalker, saying that you are to be found and escorted safely to his fortress. It would seem O' Grady decided to take some liberties in following these orders.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="30">
        <![CDATA[You are finally near the highest point of these mountains. At the top of the path, you can see a large cave. Guards stand around the entrance. You may have finally reached Stalker's fortress.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="31">
        <![CDATA[Ahead, between you and the fortress, you can see a large contingent of Hill Runners, waiting for you. ]]>
    </string>
    <string id="36">
        <![CDATA[You decide not to meet with them quite yet.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="37">
        <![CDATA[At first, you're relieved to see that the troops are led by O'Grady, the man who sent you on your mission to Zaskiva. Then you see the look on his face. His predatory scowl lets you know that he is not here to help you.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="38">
        <![CDATA[The rebels move forward, drawing their weapons. O'Grady says "It's no hope. Don't bother to fight. We know you have been going to Willow. We know you're working for Jaen. Your refusal to fight Empire troops made us sure."]]>
    </string>
    <string id="39">
        <![CDATA["We're going to take you to Stalker, but I don't think you will enjoy it. You have no choice. Surrender."]]>
    </string>
    <string id="40">
        <![CDATA[There are about 100 Hill Runners here, and more running from the fortress ahead. Even you would have difficulty when opposed by such forces. Do you surrender?]]>
    </string>
    <string id="43">
        <![CDATA[O'Grady looks relieved that you've decided to fight. He shouts the order, and leads the charge against you. You manage to kill many of them, including O' Grady, before a hail of arrows mows you down. Tough luck.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="44">
        <![CDATA[O'Grady looks disappointed. He seems to want a fight. Still, he steps out of your way, and points to the cavern ahead. "Move on. The soldiers there will take you to your cell, where Stalker will come and see you."]]>
    </string>
    <string id="45">
        <![CDATA[O'Grady and his mass of troops are still here, waiting for you to enter the fortress. It is some small measure of how seriously the rebels take you that they would leave 200 people here to guard you. They keep you from moving further south.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="46">
        <![CDATA[You reach the shores of a beautiful mountain lake. The waters are clear and blue, and the sunlight reflects off it so brightly it almost blinds you.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="47">
        <![CDATA[It would be beautiful here, were it not for the half dozen skeletons on the shore, covered with scraps of armor. Several Empire soldiers met a hard end here, and the remains were left here as a grisly trophy. Or reminder.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="48">
        <![CDATA[As you sail away from Morrow's Isle, you look back one last time. ]]>
    </string>
    <string id="49">
        <![CDATA[You had arrived expecting a noble battle against a band of brigands. You got a civil war. You expected heroics. You got treachery and deceit. And you expected good and evil, and you found desperate people, brutally tearing each other apart.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="50">
        <![CDATA[It is only a small rebellion. For now. Should the hatred and fury compressed into this small island burst forth, it could disease the continent of Valorim, and beyond.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="51">
        <![CDATA[But for now, you breathe a deep sigh of relief. It's over. You've escaped. After all, sometimes you can't win, and you can't break even. Sometimes, all you can do is get out of the game.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="52">
        <![CDATA[THE END]]>
    </string>
    <string id="54">
        <![CDATA[The boat at the end of the dock is not a complicated affair. It's a longboat, designed for easy rowing by a small crew. It will be more than enough to safely get you back to the mainland.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="55">
        <![CDATA[Are you ready to leave Morrow's Isle?]]>
    </string>
    <string id="60">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="61">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="62">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="63">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="64">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="65">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="66">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="67">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="68">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="69">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="70">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="71">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="72">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="73">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="74">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="75">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="76">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="77">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="78">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="79">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="80">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="81">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="82">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="83">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="84">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="85">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="86">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="87">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="88">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="89">
        <![CDATA[*End of special strs]]>
    </string>
</sector>
