<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<sector boes="2.0.0">
    <name>Northern Morrow&apos;s Isle</name>
    <comment>Comment</comment>
    <encounter can-flee="false" force="true">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>13</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>19</monster>
        <monster>28</monster>
        <monster>25</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </encounter>
    <wandering can-flee="true" force="false">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>13</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>19</monster>
        <monster>28</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </wandering>
    <string id="0">
        <![CDATA[A group of seedy types have set up a small fort here, in order to do things of questionable legality. Adventurers are always welcome. They gladly welcome you in.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="1">
        <![CDATA[There's all manner of brigands and rebels inside, drinking and bartering under a temporary truce. Other people are running a small bazaar of goods with a variety of origins. Do you shop?]]>
    </string>
    <string id="6">
        <![CDATA[You depart the bazaar. It doesn't appear your departure went unnoticed. A band of brigands watches you carefully as you go.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="7">
        <![CDATA[The brigands who watched you when you left the bazaar apparently decided that you looked like an easy target. They have set up an ambush for you here. They dispense with the tiresome demands for you to give up all your goods, and attack immediately.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="8">
        <![CDATA[You are surprised to find what looks like a platoon of Empire soldiers here, guarding a gate. Looking closer, you see that some are Empire defectors, and others are rebels in stolen Empire armor (with insignia removed).]]>
    </string>
    <string id="9">
        <![CDATA[Unfortunately, when you reach the gate, the guards tell you that you aren't allowed to pass. You have to turn back.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="10">
        <![CDATA[You reach a valley high up in the mountains of Morrow's Isle. The miners that have been burrowing through these mountains haven't quite reached here yet. They're still working on other areas.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="11">
        <![CDATA[The valley is quite nice and peaceful. Alpine evergreens grow all around, and bits of snow are visible here and there. No brigands. No signs of battles. It's a nice change of pace.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="16">
        <![CDATA[The road ends abruptly here, the ambitious Empire construction halted by the beginning of the war with the Hill Runners.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="17">
        <![CDATA[Bazaar of Thieves]]>
    </string>
    <string id="89">
        <![CDATA[*End of special strs]]>
    </string>
</sector>
