<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<sector boes="2.0.0">
    <name>Huge River Cavern</name>
    <comment>Comment</comment>
    <encounter can-flee="false" force="true">
        <monster>58</monster>
        <monster>60</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>68</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>12</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="-1" y="-1" />
    </encounter>
    <wandering can-flee="true" force="false">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>58</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="206" y="7" />
    </wandering>
    <wandering can-flee="true" force="false">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>60</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>62</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="206" y="7" />
    </wandering>
    <wandering can-flee="true" force="false">
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>65</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster>0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <monster friendly="true">0</monster>
        <onmeet>-1</onmeet>
        <onwin>-1</onwin>
        <onflee>-1</onflee>
        <sdf x="206" y="7" />
    </wandering>
    <sign id="0">
        <![CDATA[Upper School - 1 mi. n.|Side Entrance - 1 mi. sw.]]>
    </sign>
    <sign id="1">
        <![CDATA[Lower school - 1/4 mi. sw|Primary Waste - 1 mi. e.]]>
    </sign>
    <sign id="2">
        <![CDATA[PRIMARY WASTE STORAGE|PROTECTIVE GEAR MUST BE WORN!]]>
    </sign>
    <area top="34" left="24" bottom="41" right="40">By Filth Streams</area>
    <area top="38" left="16" bottom="40" right="20">Near School Entrance</area>
    <area top="31" left="22" bottom="32" right="25">Subterranean Bridge</area>
    <area top="23" left="8" bottom="25" right="10">By Small Cavern</area>
    <area top="3" left="12" bottom="8" right="14">Passage to School Entrance</area>
    <area top="13" left="28" bottom="22" right="41">Dying Forest</area>
    <string id="0">
        <![CDATA[You walk into an enormous cavern, and immediately run back out. The air inside is so bad, so viciously polluted, that it's a struggle merely to breathe. Your skin itches. Your eyes water and burn. You stagger out and spend a while gagging and choking.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="1">
        <![CDATA[After preparing yourselves, you walk back in and look around. Spots of light on the ceiling, created, no doubt, by the School's wizards, illuminate the cavern. It's about two miles by two miles, and dominated by the huge river winding through it.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="2">
        <![CDATA[You examine the cave carefully, trying to figure out what's befouling the air. You soon figure it out. To the southeast, there is a thin stream of gray green fluid, slowly trickling into the river. ]]>
    </string>
    <string id="3">
        <![CDATA[Upriver from the stream, the river is lined with pallid mushrooms and sickly trees. Downriver from the stream, there is diseased swamp and rubble. It's pretty compelling evidence.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="4">
        <![CDATA[On the good side, you may be close to discovering the cause of the curse. On the bad side, it seems to be a problem of a far greater scale than anyone had imagined.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="6">
        <![CDATA[Just to the north, you see a massive structure built into the cavern wall. You can't make out much detail with your bloodshot, burning eyes, but it looks like the stream of filth is trickling out of there.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="12">
        <![CDATA[From this vantage point, you can see a bit more of what is going on. The stream of poison (or filth, or demonic ichor, or whatever it is) moves very slowly and is only a few inches deep. The material is very viscous, and doesn't flow so much as ooze.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="13">
        <![CDATA[Although the stream is shallow, it's cut quite a trench out of the rock to flow down. So far, it's burned 5 feet down into the solid rock, and will probably eat its way much farther down. In addition to being smelly, it's very acidic.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="14">
        <![CDATA[The stream flows from the southeast. To find out where it comes from, that would be the place to go.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="18">
        <![CDATA[As you cross the bridge, spray from the river below coats you with a thin layer of burning water. The poisonous atmosphere of the cavern finally catches up with you.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="19">
        <![CDATA[From here, you think you can see movement in the mushroom grove to the west. You'll have to get closer to find out more.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="20">
        <![CDATA[Now you know where the occasional undead creature wandering this cavern comes from. From a hiding place on the outside of this glade, you can see a macabre dance of death going on inside.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="21">
        <![CDATA[Dozens of skeletons and zombies dance tirelessly around a bonfire, as a lone pale figure watches and joylessly claps his hands. There is a pile of bodies of all sorts nearby, probably waiting for reanimation.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="22">
        <![CDATA[None of the undead have noticed you. They seem to be following some sort of programmed motions. Maybe they'll have treasure. Or maybe they would speak with you. Or maybe they should just be left alone ...]]>
    </string>
    <string id="26">
        <![CDATA[Unfortunately, your leisurely approach gives the undead (who turn out, in fact, to be evil) plenty of time to prepare. Their vampire leader manages to cast a well placed slow spell before you reach them.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="27">
        <![CDATA[Fortunately, you manage to take them by something resembling surprise. As you rush into the circle, weapons in the air, the pale leader of the dance jumps up gleefully. You must be doing a lot to relieve the tedium.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="28">
        <![CDATA[Empire Wizards long ago figured out how to make forms of plants that could survive in caverns (many of which ended up being raised in Exile). These trees must be specimens of that sort of magic.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="29">
        <![CDATA[This subterranean forest has managed to survive the poisonous gases, but only barely. The forest is sickly and twisted, and you see many little lizard skeletons.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="30">
        <![CDATA[As if this cavern isn't unsettling enough, someone left several dead mages back here. There are four bodies. All of them were stabbed to death, and all wear the robes of apprentices (now rotted away).]]>
    </string>
    <string id="31">
        <![CDATA[The poisonous air of the cavern has eaten away at most of their possessions. One thing remains - one of them still wears a silver ring.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="36">
        <![CDATA[You feel kind of bad robbing the dead, but oh well. It's not like he was getting any use out of it.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="37">
        <![CDATA[Your victory was a miracle, and the spoils are glorious. You won't have to worry about meeting too many undead in this cavern anymore. In addition, you find some loot.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="38">
        <![CDATA[Under the vampire's chair, you find a bunch of old meat (which you leave) and gold (which you take). In addition, you get a long, slender ivory wand.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="39">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="40">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="41">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="42">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="43">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="44">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="45">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="46">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="47">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="48">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="49">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="50">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="51">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="52">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="53">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="54">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="55">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="56">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="57">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="58">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="59">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="60">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="61">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="62">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="63">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="64">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="65">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="66">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="67">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="68">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="69">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="70">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="71">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="72">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="73">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="74">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="75">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="76">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="77">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="78">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="79">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="80">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="81">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="82">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="83">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="84">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="85">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="86">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="87">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="88">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="89">
        <![CDATA[*End of special strs]]>
    </string>
</sector>
