<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<dialogue boes="2.0.0">
    <personality id="20">
        <title>Kilborn</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[The foundry is run by a lone man with excellent hair, who seems hard pressed to keep up with the job. When he sees you, however, he immediately ceases his labors to speak with you.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["I'm Kilborn. Can we make this quick? I'm looking after things by myself today."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["I'm in charge of the foundry, and I have some weapons as well. But that's not the reason why I wanted to discuss things with you."]]>
        </job>
        <unknown>
            <![CDATA["Sorry, what was that?"]]>
        </unknown>
    </personality>
    <personality id="21">
        <title>Littleford</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[You meet a wiry, perpetually annoyed woman. She paces the streets in a profoundly aggravated state. Her clothes and fingernails show the dirt of a lifetime's mining.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["Call me Littleford."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["I'm a miner. Or, at least, I was."]]>
        </job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="22">
        <title>Brown</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[Considering all the disasters that have beset the Vale recently, Blinlock's administration seems rather laid back. He runs his fingers through his hair to make sure it's straight, and leans back in his chair to speak with you.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["Just call me Brown."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["Well, I'm the administrator for the mines. Compared to what the rest of the Vale has endured, I'm having an easy time of it."]]>
        </job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="23">
        <title>Winstead</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[This woman is clearly sick, but, fortunately, not with an affliction caused by the Vale's curse. She has a cold. She's kneading a large wad of bread dough, and almost never coughs on it.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["I'm (cough) Winstead. Welcome to my shop."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["I make bread. That's what I usually do, but I have all sorts of rations on top of that."]]>
        </job>
        <unknown>
            <![CDATA[She coughs.]]>
        </unknown>
    </personality>
    <personality id="24">
        <title>Unger</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[Why a traveling merchant would want to come to Skylark Vale, you have no idea. Yet, here one is, ready to sell you wares. Maybe he got lost.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA[He pulls a massive pack off his back, opens it, and bows humbly. "I am Unger. Care to sample my wares, sir?"]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["I have all manner of wares which I have been carting about the Vale. You are lucky to catch me - I am often on the move."]]>
        </job>
        <unknown>
            <![CDATA["What on earth are you talking about? I'm a busy man, you know."]]>
        </unknown>
    </personality>
    <personality id="25">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="26">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="27">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="28">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="29">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <node for="20">
        <keyword>foun</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>if-sdf</type>
        <param>2</param>
        <param>3</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I have to look after it myself. Most people left when the mines closed. Not much metal to process, but it still keeps me busy."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Now that the mines are open, we expect to get some workers back. Until that happens, I'm on my own."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="20">
        <keyword>mine</keyword>
        <keyword>clos</keyword>
        <type>if-sdf</type>
        <param>2</param>
        <param>3</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["You should talk to Brown about that, in City Hall. He's in the market for some adventurers."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["By the way, thanks for killing all those undead. I'm sure it was a lot of fun for you."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="20">
        <keyword>purc</keyword>
        <keyword>weap</keyword>
        <type>shop</type>
        <param>5</param>
        <param>11</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[Blinlock Foundry]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="20">
        <keyword>disc</keyword>
        <keyword>thin</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["You're here to remove the curse. Well, we've all suffered by it, but I've noticed something. Nobody here seems too inclined to figure out its origins."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="20">
        <keyword>figu</keyword>
        <keyword>orig</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He smiles somewhat smugly. "I have thought about it. I don't have any answers, but I believe asking the right questions is an important step in solving any problem."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I have five questions about the curse, which must be answered if it is to be removed."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="20">
        <keyword>five</keyword>
        <keyword>ques</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Questions about the cause, the timing, the effect, the placement, and the solution."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="20">
        <keyword>caus</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["What caused the curse? The effect was so powerful and so long lasting, something very impressive must have brought it about. Why haven't we seen it?"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="21">
        <keyword>mine</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I'm a foreman at the silver digs. I keep the workers in line, and keep up to date on the latest advancements in the field."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="20">
        <keyword>timi</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Nothing unusual happened when the curse started. It just appeared out of nowhere. Isn't that peculiar?"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="20">
        <keyword>effe</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["The bitter, burning water was the first thing anyone noticed as being unusual. Why the water? What happened to it?"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="20">
        <keyword>plac</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Why Skylark Vale? Why not somewhere else? What do we have that makes us different from the other boring, dull, backwater places the Empire is full of?"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="20">
        <keyword>solu</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["How can the curse be removed? To answer that, you must go to the source. Once the first four questions are answered, the fifth should be easy."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="20">
        <keyword>answ</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He smirks. "The answers are your job."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="21">
        <keyword>fore</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[She shrugs. "Tough work. Perfect for me."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="21">
        <keyword>silv</keyword>
        <keyword>digs</keyword>
        <type>if-sdf</type>
        <param>2</param>
        <param>3</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[She spits. "Of course, I can't do anything with those damnable creatures in the pits."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Yeah, the monsters are pretty much gone. Getting workers to come back here, that's another story."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="21">
        <keyword>crea</keyword>
        <keyword>damn</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Ask Brown. He'll fill you in on what's going on in there. Good work for adventurers, if you know what I mean."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="21">
        <keyword>work</keyword>
        <keyword>line</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Yeah, I look after the workers. When we can get any, that is."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="21">
        <keyword>adva</keyword>
        <keyword>fiel</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[She looks you over, and thinks a bit. "You know, being adventurers, you might have occasion to go over to the old School of Magery. If you ever find any information that'd improve our mines, bring it here."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[She winks. "I'd make it worth your while."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="21">
        <keyword>scho</keyword>
        <keyword>mage</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I don't know much about it. It's this old school somewhere around. Closed about a century ago. The mages, they researched all sorts of things. Who knows - they might have thought about mining once or twice."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="21">
        <keyword>info</keyword>
        <keyword>impr</keyword>
        <type>call-global</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Find anything I'd like?" You respond in the negative. She frowns. "So what are you wasting my time for?"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="22">
        <keyword>vale</keyword>
        <keyword>endu</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Oddly, we've had almost no trouble with the curse. Our water is clean, the diseases minimal. Of course, the mines have been a serious problem, but nowhere near as lethal."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="22">
        <keyword>admi</keyword>
        <keyword>mine</keyword>
        <type>if-sdf</type>
        <param>2</param>
        <param>3</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["The mines situation can be summed up in one word - undead."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Now, thanks to you, the only problem with the mines is getting the workers to come back. We will cope. Thank you again." He thinks. "By the way, have you got your reward yet?"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="22">
        <keyword>unde</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>if-sdf</type>
        <param>2</param>
        <param>3</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["While digging in the mines, we accidentally exposed an ancient crypt. The spirit inside lost no time in killing some miners, summoning help, and taking over. I have a task for you, if you wish, with quite a reward."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["No more real problems with undead. Quite a relief. Your reward is well earned."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="22">
        <keyword>task</keyword>
        <keyword>rewa</keyword>
        <type>call-local</type>
        <param>10</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["The mines are at the northeast corner of town. Go in there and slay the spirit which has summoned the undead, and I will reward you well."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Beware, though. It is a wily foe. Good luck to you."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="22">
        <keyword>prob</keyword>
        <keyword>leth</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[He thinks. "I often wonder why the Vale has been so much worse off because of the curse. It certainly isn't our clean living." He chuckles. "Even our water is better."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="22">
        <keyword>wate</keyword>
        <keyword>bett</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["For what little that's worth."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="23">
        <keyword>coug</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[She coughs, not entirely turning her head away from the dough she's kneading. "Excuse me."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="23">
        <keyword>brea</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["My bread has been quite in demand in the Vale lately."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="23">
        <keyword>dema</keyword>
        <keyword>vale</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[She gives you a small bit of bread to taste. It lacks the bitter, acrid smell of the rest of the Vale's food and water. "Lately, the only way to get palatable food is to come to me. I don't know why. Just lucky, I guess."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="23">
        <keyword>purc</keyword>
        <keyword>rati</keyword>
        <type>shop</type>
        <param>5</param>
        <param>12</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[Winstead's Bakery]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="23">
        <keyword>luck</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Since the miners left, I've had nobody to sell food to."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="23">
        <keyword>mine</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I don't know much about why. Some disturbance in the mine, I guess. (cough) Brown would know more about that. He's in City Hall."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="24">
        <keyword>purc</keyword>
        <keyword>ware</keyword>
        <type>shop</type>
        <param>5</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[Unger's Wares]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="24">
        <keyword>luck</keyword>
        <keyword>move</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I often move quickly between Blinlock and Marralis. Sadly, business in the Vale has been very good."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="24">
        <keyword>marr</keyword>
        <keyword>blin</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Two towns beset by misfortune. The Vale has been very good for business."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="24">
        <keyword>busi</keyword>
        <keyword>vale</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I mainly carry adventuring supplies, which is a very safe item to be selling in any area afflicted by troubles. Between plague, bandits, and people leaving, I have been busy busy busy."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="24">
        <keyword>busy</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I am not made glad by their misfortunes, and I am more than happy to sell them the healing potions, weapons, and armor they need to get by. Of course, I am busy and cannot talk all day. Care to purchase something for yourself?"]]>
        </text>
    </node>
</dialogue>
