<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<dialogue boes="2.0.0">
    <personality id="170">
        <title>Pogue</title>
        <look>
            <![CDATA[An agitated man is standing outside your cell. He continuously looks down the corridor out of here. You notice spots of blood on his hands.]]>
        </look>
        <name>
            <![CDATA["I am Pogue. I know who you are. We don't have much time."]]>
        </name>
        <job>
            <![CDATA["I'm the interrogator for this fortress. Well, that's what I'm supposed to be. But, as you've guessed, I'm employed by Jaen."]]>
        </job>
        <unknown>
            <![CDATA[He looks nervous. "We really don't have the time for this."]]>
        </unknown>
    </personality>
    <personality id="171">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="172">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="173">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="174">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="175">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="176">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="177">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="178">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <personality id="179">
        <title>Unused</title>
        <look></look>
        <name></name>
        <job></job>
    </personality>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>inte</keyword>
        <keyword>fort</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I've been doing whatever Stalker tells me to do, to whoever he tells me to do it to. Best you don't look down on me. I saved your life. And I'm secretly employed by Jaen."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>stal</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["A wicked, brilliant, powerful man. I'm amazed that he hasn't figured me out. He'll be in his throne room, in the northwest corner of the fort."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>save</keyword>
        <keyword>life</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Stalker wanted me to start in on you right away. Flogging. Burning. You know. But he trusts my judgment, and I delayed your torture."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>dela</keyword>
        <keyword>tort</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["I told him that you would be tough to break, but if we gave you hope and took it away, it would be easier to crack you. That's why you were left in your cell, and why we left your equipment. Nothing hurts someone more than having hope, and then losing it]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["But what I was really doing is stalling, in the hope that Jaen would track you here."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>empl</keyword>
        <keyword>jaen</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Jaen is nearby! He tracked you here, and has snuck a small force to be here for you." Pogue is so nervous he can barely remain coherent. "He will be attacking soon. First, though, he sent me to free you and give you a message."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>atta</keyword>
        <keyword>soon</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["He will be sending his forces to attack here. It's not a real attack, though. He won't win. It's merely to distract Stalker's forces. That's why he sent me to give you this message."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>give</keyword>
        <keyword>mess</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[Pogue is still nervous, but his voice takes on a hard, cruel edge. You can see how he'd make a good torturer. He says, "Jaen has one last mission for you. He will be attacking and distracting the fortress, so that you can go and kill Stalker.]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["He hopes you will have no qualms about this act. After all, there will only be one penalty for failure. But great rewards for success."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>qual</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Jaen knows that sometimes adventurers have unusual qualms regarding violent acts. I can, however, assure you that, were it not for me, Stalker would have treated you to a most deliciously slow and horrible end. Do not spare any tears on his account."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>rewa</keyword>
        <keyword>succ</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[Pogue grins. "There are docks behind this fortress. There is a ship there. The stairway to the docks is beyond Stalker's fortress. Jaen's reward for you will be down there. Plus, you will be able to escape this island alive."]]>
        </text>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Of course, to get there, you'll have to go through Stalker."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>pena</keyword>
        <keyword>fail</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA[Pogue chuckles dryly. "Jaen's men will be sacrificing themselves to enable you to reach Stalker, not to save you. If you can't escape here soon, the Hill Runners will come for you and kill you."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
    <node for="170">
        <keyword>esca</keyword>
        <keyword>xxxx</keyword>
        <type>reg</type>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <param>0</param>
        <text>
            <![CDATA["Escape will be one of of your rewards for success."]]>
        </text>
    </node>
</dialogue>
